{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","address":"7444 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q Inc.","licenseNumber":"034804","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/7/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000F027F92A5CC454C0B83FB24ECF2F4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43095","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"3","pfcount":"4","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"7","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"7","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (sides)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"In large container","location":"BACK PREPARATION AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize long, shallow pans."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BACK PREPARATION AREA","subLocation":"Lack of Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"43095","inspectionDate":"8/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"42950","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2018-07-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41907","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2018-01-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41907","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"41907","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"41907","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"45161","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2018-01-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"45161","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"45161","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"45161","inspectionDate":"1/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"43916","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2017-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43916","inspectionDate":"7/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That is standing","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use cool, running water with enough flow to remove particles."},{"inspectionid":"43916","inspectionDate":"7/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."}]},{"inspectionid":"37558","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37558","inspectionDate":"12/21/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Lack of Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"37558","inspectionDate":"12/21/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."}]},{"inspectionid":"37462","establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","inspectionDate":"2016-12-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"785"}}